[{
    "question": "`9*1`",
    "answer": ["`9`", "`3`", "`6`", "`10`"],
    "correct_answer": "`9`"
},
{
    "question": "`10*5`",
    "answer": ["`51`", "`54`", "`49`", "`50`"],
    "correct_answer": "`50`"
},
{
    "question": "`4*5`",
    "answer": ["`20`", "`25`", "`23`", "`21`"],
    "correct_answer": "`20`"
},
{
    "question": "`7*5`",
    "answer": ["`35`", "`39`", "`42`", "`28`"],
    "correct_answer": "`35`"
},
{
    "question": "`5*4`",
    "answer": ["`20`", "`15`", "`19`", "`17`"],
    "correct_answer": "`20`"
},
{
    "question": "`9*11`",
    "answer": ["`99`", "`88`", "`11`", "`110`"],
    "correct_answer": "`99`"
},
{
    "question": "`3*10`",
    "answer": ["`27`", "`35`", "`30`", "`36`"],
    "correct_answer": "`30`"
},
{
    "question": "`6*6`",
    "answer": ["`37`", "`34`", "`35`", "`36`"],
    "correct_answer": "`36`"
},
{
    "question": "`5*7`",
    "answer": ["`35`", "39``", "`32`", "`30`"],
    "correct_answer": "`35`"
},
{
    "question": "`10*10`",
    "answer": ["`100`", "`60`", "`90`", "`40`"],
    "correct_answer": "`100`"
}]